allstays.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy - AllStays

**Updated 5/2018**

**PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE DOWNLOADING, USING, ACCESSING, OR PURCHASING ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE THROUGH, ANY PART OF THE ALLSTAYS WEBSITE OR SERVICES OR THE ALLSTAYS MOBILE APPLICATION (IF AVAILABLE).**

**I. OVERVIEW**

The following privacy policy (the "Policy") tells you about the information that AllStays, LLC, ("AllStays," "us," or "we") collects through its website www.allstays.com, any affiliated sub-domains, and any affiliated websites on which this Policy is posted (the "Website") and through the AllStays Mobile Applications (if available) and its services (the "Application") (collectively the Website and the Applications are referred to as the "Services") and how AllStays may use or disclose that collected information.

By accessing the Services, continuing to access the Services, purchasing any products or services through the Services, downloading and/or using the Application, or submitting any information through the Services, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us, as described below. Your use of the Services is also governed by the Terms of Service which are expressly incorporated into this Policy.

**II. UPDATES**

AllStays reserves the right to make changes to this Policy at any time, and will post any revised Policy on this page. You will know we have changed the Policy when you see a new updated date at the top of this Policy. AllStays will not notify the Services' users of any such changes by email or other personal contact. We encourage you to check the date of this Policy whenever you visit the Services so that you will know when you need to review the Policy for modifications.

**III. INFORMATION COLLECTION**

**Age Restriction.** AllStays does not intend to use the Services to collect any information from children under age 18. By submitting any information through the Services, you represent and warrant that you are older than age 18.

**Collection of Submitted Information.** AllStays may collect and store any information you submit or upload through the Services, whether through your submission of information through a form, purchase of a subscription or product, or otherwise. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, email address, telephone number, payment information, or any other information submitted by you or any user through the Services.

**Collection from Third-Parties.** AllStays may collect information about you from third-parties, including from any account through which you log into, or otherwise interact with, AllStays (e.g., Facebook or Google). If applicable, AllStays may have access to certain information from your linked Google or Facebook account, including your public profile information, your email address, or other information possessed by those third-parties. AllStays may aggregate any information about you collected from any source.

**Passive Information Collection.** AllStays may also collect, either directly or through the use of one or more services or analytics providers, passive information about your device, visit, or use of the Services, including, but not limited to, the date and time of your visit, the length of your visit, the specific webpages you visited, your IP address, your geographic location, the type of web browser and operating system used, the address of any website that directed you to the Services, and information about your mobile device used to access the Services (including phone number, operating system details, and any applicable unique identifiers for you or your device, including your devices' Unique Device Identifier (UDID), any Apple or iOS identifiers (e.g., IDFA or an Advertising Identifier), any Google or Android identifiers (e.g., Android or Google Advertising ID), any Windows identifiers (e.g., Windows Advertising ID), or any other similar identifiers which identify you or your device). AllStays may collect and aggregate usage information related to your use of the Services.

**Cookies and Related Technologies.** We, or other third-parties assisting us, may use cookies, web beacons, local shared objects (sometimes called "flash cookies"), or other similar technology in connection with your use of the Services (collectively, "Cookies"). Cookies are small data files that may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Services, such as your browser type, search preferences, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may track activities over time and across websites. You can disable some (but not all) Cookies in your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect your ability to use the services provided through the Services.

**Third-Party Vendors and Advertisers.** AllStays may use third-party vendors or advertisers to collect and analyze information about your use of the Services. These third-parties may use cookies or other similar mechanisms to provide us with information and analysis about your use of the Services. This information collection and analysis allows us to better understand how the Services are being used so that we can strive to provide the most relevant content to our users. These third-parties may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites. This information may be used to serve interest-based advertisements on our website or other websites or applications across the internet. We may combine information gathered from one or more of these services.

**Applications.** By purchasing and/or downloading an Application, you are disclosing certain personal and payment information to the applicable company (e.g., Apple or Google). That company may disclose some or all of your collected information to AllStays.

**Analytics Services.** AllStays may, from time to time, use one or more analytics service providers, including, for example, Google, Facebook, or others. If AllStays uses a Google analytics service, it may use any of the following Google analytics features: AdWords, Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. We may combine information gathered from one or more of these services. AllStays may use other analytics services from time to time. 

For information on how Google collects and uses the information collected through AllStays' use of the Google analytics and advertising services, if applicable, see the Google, Inc. Privacy Policy here (https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

For more information about the Google analytics features used by AllStays, if applicable, click here (https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2404395?hl=en&ref_topic=1631776&rd=1).

For information on how to see and change your Google Ad Settings, click here (https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662856?hl=en).

**For information on the use of the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On** , click here (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). However, AllStays does not necessarily endorse this add-on and does not guarantee that using the add-on will be effective.

For more information on how Facebook Analytics may collect and use the information collected through AllStays's use of the Facebook's analytics and advertising services, if applicable, see the Facebook data use policy and related policies here. (https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy).

The Services may, from time to time, also include social media functions allowing you to like or share content on social media platforms like Facebook or Twitter. These features may collect your information through the use of cookies or other technologies. These features may be hosted by a third-party and governed by the third-party's privacy policy.

AllStays does not guarantee that it will take action in response to do-not-track signals or similar mechanisms. Additionally, some third-party service providers may still collect tracking information even if you have enabled your browser's do-not-track functionality or utilized a similar do-not-track mechanism.

**IV. INFORMATION USE PRACTICES**

AllStays may use the collected information or data described above, individually or in the aggregate, for any lawful purpose, including, but not limited to, such purposes as fulfilling product orders, analyzing and tracking user activity on the Services for individual users or for groups of users, tracking and analyzing usage trends, personalizing the Services to better reflect your preferences, serving more relevant advertisements, or enhancing your and other users' use of the Services. All collected information may be linked to specific website users and may result in the tracking of the usage information for individual users.

If you submit a review or other feedback to us, we may use that to improve the services and may publicly display that review or feedback.

**AllStays may also use your submitted information to contact you, via regular mail, email, text message, telephone, or otherwise, regarding your account, the Services, your purchased services or products, or other relevant or promotional information or offers as determined by AllStays or its partners. By submitting your contact information to AllStays or AllStays' partners, you consent to receiving such communications.**

**V. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

Except for the limitations expressly discussed herein, if any, AllStays may disclose, sell, or transfer any collected information to third-parties for any lawful purpose in our sole discretion.

**Geographic Location.** By using the Applications, you may be sending information about your geographic location to third-party map providers integrated with the Applications. These providers could include Mapbox, Open Street Map, Apple Maps, and/or Google Maps. Please review the privacy policies for those providers (as applicable).

**Third-Party Services.** If you log in to AllStays through a third-party service like Facebook or Google, then those third-parties may have access to certain information about your use of AllStays. For more information on the type of information those third-parties may collect about you, please review the privacy policies for those third-parties.

**Vendors.** AllStays may use third-party companies, agents, or contractors to perform services on our behalf. For example, AllStays may partner with other companies to personalize our web pages, provide maps and location services, analyze our website or usage information, process payments or credit card transactions, fulfill or ship orders, detect fraud, collect debts, analyze or enhance the data collected by the Services (including user's interaction with the Services), or otherwise assist AllStays in better serving the Services' users. During the course of providing AllStays with these services, these third-parties may have access to your personal and non-personal information in order to provide the services we requested from those third-parties.

**Affiliates and Marketing.** AllStays may disclose your collected information, including information about any purchases you make through the Services, to AllStays' affiliated entities. AllStays may also disclose your information to third-parties for marketing purposes. These affiliates and third-parties may contact you via any method of contact you provide to AllStays.

**Legal Compliance.** AllStays also reserves the right to disclose personal information when we reasonably believe disclosure is required by law, if we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary to establish or exercise legal rights, or in situations involving potential threats to physical safety.

**Merger or Acquisition.** In the event that AllStays is acquired by or merged with a third-party, we reserve the right to sell or otherwise transfer any and all information we have collected from you as part of that transaction and such third-party will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Policy.

**VI. THIRD-PARTY LINKS**

The Services may contain links to websites not owned or controlled by AllStays. AllStays does not necessarily review or endorse the content of these linked websites. You should review the terms of service and privacy policies of all websites you visit.

**VII. SECURITY**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information we collect on the Services. Unfortunately, however, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% effective. Accordingly, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it.

You are responsible for restricting access to your computer or mobile device through which you access the Services. Users of public or shared computers or unprotected mobile devices should log out at the completion of each visit to our Services. By using the Services, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of these Services.

**VIII. DATA RETENTION**

AllStays may retain the personal and non-personal information or other collected data, individually or in the aggregate, as described above, after you delete your account or have ceased using the Services. However, AllStays does not guarantee that any information will continue to be available after such deletion or cessation.

**IX. VIEWING AND UPDATING INFORMATION**

You are responsible for updating and maintaining the accuracy of your personal information that you provide to or through the Services. If you believe you have submitted inaccurate information through the Services, and would like AllStays to change such information, please contact AllStays at the address below.

**X. CONTACT**

If you have questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please contact AllStays at the following address:

AllStays, LLC  
PMB 466  
7 Avenida Vista Grande B-7  
Santa Fe, NM 87508  
web@allstays.com  

1877790.01
